milonic.com 2004-12-06

# Milonic Solutions Privacy Policy

### Milonic Solutions Privacy Policy

Milonic Solutions are registered with the UK's Data Protection Registrar.  
Our Registration number is **PZ7648184**

* * *

**_PURPOSE_**  
Milonic Solutions is committed to protecting your privacy. The following discloses our information collection and use practices for our Website.

**_PERSONAL INFORMATION_**  
When you place an order, download any code, or join a discussion list, we ask for your contact information, which is then used for our internal operations and to provide you with updated information on any of our products.

  * We may contact you about updates to our products  

  * We will never sell, trade or rent your personal information to others  

  * We will make every effort to secure the personal data we store 

**_CERTAIN EXCEPTIONAL DISCLOSURES_**  
We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct. Disclosure may be required by law, or if we receive legal process.

**_USE OF COOKIES_**  
We use "cookies" to help create a more effective and convenient site experience. By showing us how and when visitors use the site, "cookies" help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on data such as total number of visitors and pages viewed. Milonic Solutions does not store any sensitive information in a cookie other than name, email address & web site URL. 

**_CHOICE TO OPT-OUT_**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the user. If you would like to opt-out send email to [privacy@milonic.com](mailto:mmprivacy@milonic.com)

**_OTHER SITES_**  
This site contains links to other sites. Milonic Solutions is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**_YOUR CONSENT TO THIS POLICY_**  
By using our site, you agree to this Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. We may change it by posting a new version on our site at any time.

_**REVIEWING PERSONAL DATA**_  
You can review and validate the information, that we have collected about you by sending email to [info@milonic.com](mailto:mminfo@milonic.com)

**_CONTACTING THE WEB SITE_**  
If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web Site, you can contact: [privacy@milonic.com](mailto:mmprivacy@milonic.com)

The law on spam email
